Guide to the Historical Planning publications collection, 1888-2002.
Historical Planning publications collection
- Series XXVII. Regional Planning
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Great Britain, 1942-1956 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - India, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Latin America (1), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Latin America (2), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Latin America (3), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Malaya (Oversized), 19 (Box 61)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Mexico, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Netherlands, 1958-1967 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - South Africa, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - United Arab Republic, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Yugoslavia, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Regional Planning - General (1), 1923-1970 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Regional Planning - General (2), 1923-1970 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Regional Planning - Pennsylvania (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Regional Planning - San Francisco Bay Region, 1950-1960 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Regional Planning - San Francisco Bay Region, 1930-1940 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Regional Planning - San Francisco Bay Region, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Regional Planning - TVA - Press handbook, 1960-1970 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Regional Planning - TVA - Operations, 1950-1960 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Regional Planning - TVA - Operations, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Regional Planning - TVA - Power Annual Report, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Regional Planning - TVA - Power Annual Report, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Illinois (1), 1932-1963 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Illinois (2), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Illinois-Indiana, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Illinois (2), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Kansas City Metropolitan Area, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Louisiana, 1958-1963 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Maryland (1), 1951-1962 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Maryland (2), 1967-1977 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1958-1962 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Michigan (1), 1941 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Michigan (2), 1942-1960 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Missouri, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Missouri River Basin (1), 1941-1944 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Missouri River Basin (2), 1958 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New England (1), 1934-1935 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New England (2), 1936-1937 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New England (3), 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New England (4), 1941-1943 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New Jersey, 1945-1968 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New York, 1939-1969 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New York - New York City Metropolitan Area, 1922-1969 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New York - Niagra Frontier (1), 1925-1941 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New York - Niagra Frontier (2), 1943-1960 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - New York - Niagra Frontier (3), 1977-1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - North Carolina, 1952-1973 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Texas (1), 1960 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Texas (2), 1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Texas - Gulf Coast (Oversized), 1967 (Box 23)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Texas - Gulf Coast (Oversized), 1967 (Box 62)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Vermont, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Virginia, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Virginia, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Washington - Metropolitan Area, 1930,1950-1970 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Washington - Metropolitan Area, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Washington, 1960-1970 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Ohio, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Oklahoma, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Pacific Northwest, 1930-1940, 60 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Pacific Southwest, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1940-1960 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Philadelphia - Tri-State District (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Piscatagua Area of N.H. & Maine, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Delaware River Basin (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Potomac River Basin, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Puerto Rico, 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Rocky Mountains, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - St.Lawrence River, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Southeast, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Southwest, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Southwest, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Tennessee, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - St.Lawrence River, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Southeast, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Southeast, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Southwest, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Tennessee, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1950-1970 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1950-1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1950-1960 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Alabama, Coosa Drainage Basin, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - California (1), 1942-1975 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - California (2), 1942-1975 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Colorado, 1933-1978 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Columbia Valley, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Connecticut (1), 1948-1969 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Connecticut (2), 1948-1969 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Florida, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Regional Planning - U.S. - Georgia, 1962-1967 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Series XXVIII. Sanitation
  - Sanitation - Foreign - Canada, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Sanitation - General (1), 1946-1959 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Sanitation - General (2), 1962-1968 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Sanitation - U.S. - Illinois, 1942-1957 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Sanitation - U.S. - Maryland, 1958-1960 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Sanitation - U.S. - Michigan (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Sanitation - U.S. - North Carolina, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Sanitation - U.S. - Ohio, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Sanitation - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Sanitation - U.S. - Tennessee, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Series XXIX. Schools
  - Schools - General, 1936-1961 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Schools - U.S. - Arizona, 1960-1962 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Schools - U.S. - Arkansas, 1954-1957 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Schools - U.S. - California, 1956-1962 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Schools - U.S. - Connecticut, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Schools - U.S. - Illinois, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Schools - U.S. - Iowa, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Schools - U.S. - Louisiana, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Schools - U.S. - Maine, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Schools - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Schools - U.S. - Michigan, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Schools - U.S. - Missouri, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Schools - U.S. - New Jersey, 1945-1968 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Schools - U.S. - New York (1), 1945-1948 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Schools - U.S. - New York (2), 1948-1949 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Schools - U.S. - New York (3), 1952-1959 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Schools - U.S. - New York (4), 1960-1966 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Schools - U.S. - North Carolina, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Schools - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1960-1961 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Schools - U.S. - Rhose Island, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Schools - U.S. - Tennessee, 1956-1957 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Schools - U.S. - Tennessee (Oversized), 1959 (Box 61)
  - Schools - U.S. - Texas, 1948-1960 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Schools - U.S. - Virginia, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Schools - U.S. - Washington (State), 1955-1966 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Schools - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1924-1951 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Series XXX. Shopping Centers
  - Shopping Centers - General, 1946-1963 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Arizona, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - California, 1944-1965 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Hawaii, 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Illinois, 1953-1968 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Iowa (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Maryland, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Massachuestts, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Michigan, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Missouri (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - New York, 1953-1961 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Shopping Centers - U.S. - Ohio, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Shopping Centers - Foreign - England, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Series XXXI. Social Planning
  - Social Planning - General (1), 1956-1969 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Social Planning - General (2), 1970 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Social Planning - Aging, 1958-1970 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Social Planning - Directories, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Social Planning - Education, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Social Planning - Manpower Development and Training, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Social Planning - Minorities, 1965-1968 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Social Planning - Social Surveys (1), 1929-1937 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Social Planning - Social Surveys (2), 1940-1956 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Social Planning - Social Surveys (3), 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Social Planning - Social Surveys (4), 1965-1966 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Social Planning - Social Surveys (5), 1967 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Social Planning - Social Surveys - U.S. - Michigan - Detroit (Oversized), 1955 (Box 69)
  - Social Planning - Welfare and Social Service, 1960-1969 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Social Planning - Youth Programs, 1939-1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Series XXXII. States
  - States - General (1), 1933-1957 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - States - General (2), 1935-1942 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - States - General (3), 1935-1942 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - States - General (4), 1934-1940 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - States - Alabama, 1942-1947 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - States - Alaska, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - States - Arkansas, 1934-1957 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - States - Arizona, 1934-1935 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - States - California, 1945-1963 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - States - Colorado, 1934-1960 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - States - Connecticut, 1934-1959 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - States - District of Columbia, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - States - Florida, 1934-1944 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - States - Florida (Oversized), 1939 (Box 61)
  - States - Hawaii, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - States - Idaho, 1934-1940 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - States - Illinois (1), 1934 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - States - Illinois (2), 1935-1944 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - States - Illinois (3), 1944-1968 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - States - Indiana, 1944-1967 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - States - Iowa, 1936-1961 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - States - Kansas, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - States - Kentucky, 1951-1958 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - States - Louisiana (1), 1941 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - States - Louisiana (2), 1945 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - States - Maine, 1941-1967 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - States - Maryland, 1942-1948 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - States - Massachusetts, 1929-1957 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - States - Michigan (1), 1937-1946 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - States - Michigan (2), 1947-1967 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - States - Minnesota, 1934-1965 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - States - New Hampshire (1), 1936-1944 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - States - New Hampshire (2), 1949-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - States - New York (1), 1935-1953 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - States - New York (2), 1957-1966 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - States - New York (3), 1935 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - States - New York (4), 1936 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - States - New York (5), 1937-1941 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - States - New York (6), 1945-1946 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - States - New York (7), 1947-1964 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - States - New Jersey (1), 1935-1938 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - States - New Jersey (2), 1950-1951 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - States - New Jersey (3), 1952-1966 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - States - New Jersey (Oversized), 1944 (Box 61)
  - States - New Mexico (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - States - North Carolina, 1946-1967 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - States - North Dakota, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - States - Ohio, 1944-1969 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - States - Oregon, 1936-1968 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - States - Pennsylvania, 1937-1968 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - States - Puerto Rico, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - States - Rhode Island (1), 1935-1942 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - States - Rhode Island (2), 1943-1969 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - States - South Dakota (1), 1935-1938 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - States - South Dakota (2), 1936 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - States - South Carolina, 1937-1947 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - States - Tennessee (1), 1942-1945 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - States - Tennessee (2), 1946-1949 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - States - Tennessee (3), 1952 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - States - Tennessee (4), 1957-1962 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - States - Texas, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - States - Utah, 1941-1943 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - States - Vermont, 1935-1951 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - States - Virginia (1), 1934-1942 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - States - Virginia (2), 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - States - Virginia (3), 1945-1946 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - States - Washington, 1935-1942 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - States - West Virginia, 1941-1942 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - States - Wisconsin, 1949-1968 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Series XXXIII. Transportation
  - Transportation - General (1), 1923-1934 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Transportation - General (2), 1935-1936 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Transportation - General (3), 1942-1944 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Transportation - General (4), 1945-1949 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Transportation - General (5), 1940-1949 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Transportation - General (6), 1950-1952 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Transportation - General (7), 1953-1956 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Transportation - General (8), 1957-1959 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Transportation - General (9), 1960-1967 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Transportation - General (10), 1968-1973 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Transportation - U.S., 1968 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Alaska, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Arkansas, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - California (1), 1943-1960 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - California (2), 1961-1963 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - California (3), 1964-1980 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - California (Oversized), 1962 (Box 62)
  - Transportation - Colorado, 1932 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Florida, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Georgia, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Great Lakes, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Transportation - Hawaii, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Transportation - Illinois, 1958-1960 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Transportation - Iowa, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Transportation - Kansas, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Transportation - Kentucky, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Transportation - Maine, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Transportation - Maryland, 1950-1955 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Transportation - Massachusetts, 1947-1967 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Transportation - Michigan, 1928-1948 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Transportation - Minnesota, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Transportation - Missouri (1), 1920-1969 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Transportation - Missouri (2), 1969 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Transportation - New Jersey (1), 1939-1946 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Transportation - New Jersey (2), 1955-1962 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Transportation - New York (1), 1925-1940 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - New York (2), 1944-1949 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - New York (3), 1954-1959 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - New York (4), 1916-1930 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - New York (5), 1958-1966 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - U.S. - New York (Oversized), 1969 (Box 69)
  - Transportation - Ohio, 1924-1972 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Oregon, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Pennsylvania (1), 1957-1960 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Pennsylvania (2), 1961-1970 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Rhode Island, 1943-1953 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Transportation - Tennessee, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Transportation - Texas, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Transportation - Washington, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Transportation - Wisconsin, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Transportation - Wyoming, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Transportation - Foreign - Canada (1), 1946-1960 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Transportation - Foreign - Canada (2), 1963-1967 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Transportation - Foreign - England, 1959-1964 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Transportation - Foreign - India, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Transportation - Foreign - Japan, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Transportation - Authorities, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Transportation - Commuting, 1943-1968 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Transportation - Finance, 1954-1962 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Transportation - Legal Aspects, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Transportation - Studies - Techniques and Research, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Series XXXIV. Urbanization
  - Urbanization - Arkansas, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Urbanization - California (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Urbanization - Michigan, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Urbanization - New York State, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Urbanization - Ohio, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Urbanization - Texas, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Urbanization - Utah, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Urbanization - Indonesia, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Urbanization - Canada, 1952-1956 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Urbanization - Netherlands, 1958-1958 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Urbanization - Great Britain, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Urbanization - General (1), 1941-1970 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Urbanization - General (2), 1923-1966 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Series XXXV. Urban Renewal
  - Urban Renewal - Administration, 1942-1956 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - General, 1935-1980 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - California, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - Delaware, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - Illinois, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - Maryland, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - Michigan, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - New Jersey, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - New York, 1954-1959 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - North Carolina, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - Ohio, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal - Blighted Areas - Oregon, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal - Conservation - Washington, D.C., 1960 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - Finance, 1960-1964 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal - Foreign, 1944-1950 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal - General (1), 1933-1949 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - General (2), 1950-1954 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - General (3), 1955-1957 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal - General (4), 1958 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal - General (5), 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal - General (6), 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal - General (7), 1965-1970 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal - General (8), 1958-1959 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - General(Oversized), 1957 (Box 69)
  - Urban Renewal - Law (1), 1943-1956 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal - Law (2), 1946 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal - Law (3), 1958-1965 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - California, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Colorado (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - District of Columbia, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Illinois, 1947-1957 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Maryland, 1949-1956 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Massachusetts, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Montana, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Nevada, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - New York, 1940-1944 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Oklahoma, circa 1954 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Rhode Island, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Tennessee (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Virginia, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal - Law - Washington, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Urban Renewal - Plans - Rhode Island, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Urban Renewal - Plans - Foreign - Puerto Rico (Oversized), 1957 (Box 61)
  - Urban Renewal - Public Relations, 1947-1957 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - General, 1937-1963 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Alabama, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Alabama (Oversized), 1966-1977 (Box 62)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Arkansas (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - California (1), 1947-1949 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Californiat (2), 1950-1954 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - California (3), 1955-1959 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - California (4), 1960-1967 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Colorado (Oversized) (Box 62)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Connecticut (1), 1958 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Connecticut (2), 1958-1967 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - District of Columbia, 1952-1969 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Hawaii, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Illinois (1), 1940-1949 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Illinois (2), 1950-1954 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Illinois (3), 1955-19657 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Illinois (4), 1958-1959 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Illinois (5), 1960-1969 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Indiana (1), 1948-1949 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Indiana (2), 1951-1957 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Louisiana (Oversized), 1963 (Box 70)
  - Urban Development - Redevelopment - Louisiana - Monroe (Oversized), 196? (Box 62)